<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Recipes</string>
    <string name="titleText1">"PB&amp;J Sandwich"</string>
    <string name="titleText2">"Cereal with Milk"</string>
    <string name="titleText3">"Banana Smoothie"</string>
    <string name="titleText4">"Avocado Toast"</string>
    <string name="titleText5">"Boiled Eggs"</string>
    <string name="titleText6">"Grilled Cheese Sandwich"</string>
    <string name="titleText7">"Pasta Aglio e Olio"</string>
    <string name="titleText8">"Fruit Salad"</string>
    <string name="titleText9">"Guacamole"</string>
    <string name="titleText10">"Scrambled Eggs"</string>
    <string name="titleText11">"Stir-Fried Vegetables"</string>
    <string name="titleText12">"Pancakes"</string>
    <string name="titleText13">"Chicken Caesar Salad"</string>
    <string name="titleText14">"Vegetable Soup"</string>
    <string name="titleText15">"Tacos"</string>
    <string name="titleText16">"Spaghetti Bolognese"</string>
    <string name="titleText17">"Baked Chicken Drumsticks"</string>
    <string name="titleText18">"Rice Pilaf"</string>
    <string name="titleText19">"Grilled Salmon"</string>
    <string name="titleText20">"Lasagna"</string>
    <string name="titleText21">"Beef Stir-Fry with Noodles"</string>
    <string name="titleText22">"Roast Chicken"</string>
    <string name="titleText23">"Mushroom Risotto"</string>
    <string name="titleText24">"Chicken Alfredo Pasta"</string>
    <string name="titleText25">"Homemade Pizza"</string>
    <string name="titleText26">"Beef Stew"</string>
    <string name="titleText27">"Sushi Rolls"</string>
    <string name="titleText28">"Beef Wellington"</string>
    <string name="titleText29">"Chocolate Cake"</string>
    <string name="titleText30">"Croissants"</string>

    <string name="contentText1">"Spread peanut butter on one slice of bread and jelly on another. Put them together to form a sandwich."</string>
    <string name="contentText2">"Pour your favorite cereal into a bowl and add milk."</string>
    <string name="contentText3">"Blend a banana with a cup of milk or yogurt until smooth."</string>
    <string name="contentText4">"Mash avocado onto toasted bread slices. Sprinkle with salt, pepper, and red pepper flakes."</string>
    <string name="contentText5">"Place eggs in a pot, cover with water, and bring to a boil. Boil for 8–10 minutes, then cool and peel."</string>
    <string name="contentText6">"Butter two slices of bread, place cheese between them, and grill until golden and crispy."</string>
    <string name="contentText7">"Cook spaghetti until al dente. In a pan, heat olive oil and minced garlic. Toss cooked pasta with oil, garlic, red pepper flakes, and parsley."</string>
    <string name="contentText8">"Chop a variety of fruits (e.g., strawberries, kiwi, mango, and pineapple) and mix in a bowl. Optionally, squeeze some lemon juice over the top."</string>
    <string name="contentText9">"Mash avocados and mix with diced onions, tomatoes, cilantro, lime juice, salt, and pepper."</string>
    <string name="contentText10">"Whisk eggs with a splash of milk, cook in a pan over medium heat, stirring until softly scrambled."</string>
    <string name="contentText11">"Heat oil in a pan, add chopped vegetables (e.g., bell peppers, broccoli, carrots), season with soy sauce, and stir-fry until tender."</string>
    <string name="contentText12">"Mix flour, sugar, baking powder, salt, milk, eggs, and melted butter until smooth. Cook spoonfuls of batter on a hot griddle until bubbles form, then flip and cook until golden brown."</string>
    <string name="contentText13">"Grill chicken breasts, slice, and serve over romaine lettuce with Caesar dressing, croutons, and Parmesan cheese."</string>
    <string name="contentText14">"Sauté onions, carrots, celery, and garlic in a pot. Add broth, diced tomatoes, and your choice of vegetables. Simmer until vegetables are tender."</string>
    <string name="contentText15">"Cook ground beef with taco seasoning. Fill taco shells with meat, shredded lettuce, diced tomatoes, cheese, and salsa."</string>
    <string name="contentText16">"Cook ground beef with onions and garlic. Add tomato sauce and simmer. Serve over cooked spaghetti with grated Parmesan."</string>
    <string name="contentText17">"Rub chicken drumsticks with olive oil and seasonings. Bake in the oven until golden and cooked through."</string>
    <string name="contentText18">"Sauté onion and garlic in butter. Add rice and cook until lightly toasted. Stir in chicken broth and simmer until rice is cooked."</string>
    <string name="contentText19">"Season salmon fillets with salt, pepper, and lemon juice. Grill until fish is cooked through and flakes easily with a fork."</string>
    <string name="contentText20">"Layer cooked lasagna noodles with meat sauce, ricotta cheese mixture, and shredded mozzarella. Bake until bubbly and golden."</string>
    <string name="contentText21">"Marinate beef strips in soy sauce, ginger, and garlic. Stir-fry with vegetables and cooked noodles."</string>
    <string name="contentText22">"Rub a whole chicken with olive oil, salt, pepper, and herbs. Roast in the oven until golden and cooked through."</string>
    <string name="contentText23">"Sauté mushrooms and onions in butter. Add Arborio rice and gradually stir in chicken broth until creamy."</string>
    <string name="contentText24">"Cook pasta, grill chicken, and toss with Alfredo sauce, grated Parmesan, and chopped parsley."</string>
    <string name="contentText25">"Make pizza dough, roll it out, top with sauce, cheese, and toppings, and bake until crust is crispy and cheese is bubbly."</string>
    <string name="contentText26">"Brown beef cubes in a pot. Add onions, carrots, potatoes, and beef broth. Simmer until meat and vegetables are tender."</string>
    <string name="contentText27">"Spread sushi rice on nori sheets, add fillings (e.g., cucumber, avocado, cooked shrimp), and roll tightly. Slice and serve with soy sauce and wasabi."</string>
    <string name="contentText28">"Wrap beef tenderloin in puff pastry with a layer of mushroom duxelles. Bake until pastry is golden brown and meat is cooked to your liking."</string>
    <string name="contentText29">"Mix flour, sugar, cocoa powder, baking powder, baking soda, eggs, milk, oil, and vanilla. Bake in a cake pan until a toothpick inserted comes out clean. Frost as desired."</string>
    <string name="contentText30">"Make laminated dough by folding butter into layers of dough. Roll out, cut into triangles, roll up into crescents, and bake until golden brown and flaky."</string>
</resources>
